Raul Alpizar

Analyst and software developer

Miami, FL - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Raul-Alpizar/6940148761df974c

An innovative thinker, initiative taker and multi-dimensional professional with exceptional logical and analytical skills possesses 7+ experience as a computer science engineer. Experience in designing, developing, implementing and testing computer-based hardware and software. Expert in working on integrating software programs with computer hardware.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Pet's Area Code - Miami, FL - March 2017 to Present

Software Developer

Smartness Creative - Miami, FL - November 2016 to Present

Analyst and software developer

Estudio XOCH - Merida - August 2015 to June 2016

Informatics and IT Department General Manager

ONBC Cienfuegos - Cienfuegos - June 2014 to August 2015

Teacher

Cienfuegos University - August 2010 to May 2013

Discrete Math, Logic Math, Descriptive Programming, Artificial Intelligence)

- Innovator Forecast System Project Manager.

EDUCATION

Master's in Math Applied.

Cienfuegos University - Cuba, MO January 2011 to November 2013

Bachelor's in Informatics Engineering

Cienfuegos University - Cuba, MO September 2004 to July 2010

IPVCE Carlos Roloff High School - Cuba, MO September 2001 to July 2004

LINKS

http://meveosiqueiros.mx

http://www.allpetsuppliesoutlet.com

http://www.bottontextil.com/prueba

http://www.smartnesscreative.com

http://www.universalgymnastics.net

https://xoch.mx

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills:

- Knowledge and skills in different programming languages. (C++, C#, Java, PHP, XML).
- Proven experience with object-oriented languages.
- Strong experience with MVC (4.0+), HTML5 and CSS3.
- Experience with modern CSS and JavaScript frameworks (JQuery, Knockout, Bootstrap, LESS, etc.)
- RDBMS experience, ideally SQL Server, MySQL, Postgre, Oracle (Stored Procedures, Triggers, Views, Indexes, Functions, etc.)
- Working knowledge of object-oriented software design and design patterns.
- Experience with MS Visual Studio, Netbeans, Eclipse, Atom, C++ Builder, Zend Studio, Android Studio, Stylizer, Photoshop & Illustrator & After Effects.
- Web design and Programming knowledge (Java Script, JQuery, JSON, WordPress, Joomla.)
- Knowledge and professional skills, Web and App developer, Front-end and Back-end development/design, E-Commerce, Data Mining, Math algorithm and logic.
- Ability to work with technical and nontechnical people.
- Able to learn new technologies quickly and as needed.
- Ability to conduct research and resolve technical application issues.